in a video pretty recently about
How you can practice prepositions by reading and listening
and I was going to tip about about the same way to
consider when it comes to verbs
And then I think like this that if you
beats up a grammar book or
Maybe find a piece of paper with a list of many many verbs
Then it is very easy to feel that
This is what I will never learn, this is too much
It is too difficult
it won't get stuck in memory
example
Then you will still learn between
Say 300 and 150 verbs
In that group in one year
and you probably don't need a huge number to
manage in most situations
so
What I want to say with this movie is
that if you have a hard time learning a lot of grammar
at one time I don't think you need to stress so much
without